[{"answer": "This process has been messy.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 3, "question": "But is anybody in Washington really happy now?", "qSentId": 2}, {"answer": "This agreement cast a long- term shadow on our nation's reasonableness and our reliability.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 8, "question": "Will this make the economy even worse?", "qSentId": 7}, {"answer": "The American people hold us and their low opinion of us, because we are failing to do what they think is our job, and by the way, they are right.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "Has Congress shot itself in the foot?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "It was very emotional, and understandably so, because we really haven't seen much of her a little bit when her husband took off on the shuttle, but there she was.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "No one expected that and it was really not a dry eye in the House, right?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "Probably the Tea Party supporters have come out of it pretty well because they did manage successfully to get this entire issue linked, reducing the national debt and raising the debt ceiling.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Who's come out of this badly?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "I think that's a pretty good way of putting it.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "And pretty much stabbed the speaker, John Boehner flat in the back, didn't they?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Nobody really seems to believe, Erin, that anything in this deal is actually going to stimulate the American economy and that in itself is incredibly serious, isn't it?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "It's going to be a tough one.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Very quickly, Erin, predictions for the markets tomorrow morning?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "LITZER: I don't think his position is in jeopardy.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Could his position be in jeopardy?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Well, I think the American people won in that we were able to bring down the deficit in this first step.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Where did you win and where did you lose in this debate?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Well, it was extraordinary.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "I have decided I will not vote for the bill, although I really respect the people who've worked on it and the fact that it does take some real progress toward reducing spending, although far less than we need.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Senator Sessions, how will you be voting tomorrow?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "No, I know -- I think the Tea Party movement represented a spontaneous American expression of shock and concern over the spending that was going on in Washington.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "What do you say of that?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "I embrace it.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "As a Republican, are you concerned about that or do you embrace it?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "It really was.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "I mean it was tear-jerking, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "UPTA: Well, you know what, when you think about, you know, cognition overall, Piers, it's sort of two ways to divide it.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Can she have normal conversation?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Well, I think so.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "And from a therapeutic point of view, Sanjay, would something like today with the outpouring of emotion and everything else, would that be seen as a good thing, do you think, for her?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Well, then you would have assumed wrong obviously.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "So I can only assume that you would have been quite happy for your country to go into catastrophic default?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Of course, I don't believe that.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "And finally, Congressman, presumably, you believe that Speaker Boehner should now resign given he's authorized this terrible deal?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "I didn't stab him in the back.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "If he's done such a great job, why did you stab him in the back?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "For saying things like that, Piers.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "I say that, Piers, because here we have a major crisis in the country.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Arianna, why do you say that?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Apparently, yeah.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Did Nancy Pelosi say that, too?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Well, the Tea Party was allowed to call the shots.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "So the Tea Party, really, have been calling the shots with both sides?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Well, that is really the problem, Piers.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "What do you think today's deal, and the Senate presumably approving it tomorrow, will actually do for parents and families in America?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Well, I'm ultimately an optimist.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Do you fear that America, despite all of the protestations to the contrary, that America could go through the same thing that Greece has been through?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Well, I believe that there should have been tax increases, if only for a political matter, because everybody in the country, it seems to me, has to be seen to be participating in what I call shared sacrifice.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "What was your view?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Well, it moves us at least in the right direction.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Here's the question for you, if I get you back on the show in a month's time, are you absolutely certain this no taxation at any cost policy of yours will mean that the economy will have recovered?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "I don't think that putting leaches on a patient is ever a good idea.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "At what point do you and the Republicans that agree with your position on taxation stop and think actually we have to consider it?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Well, that's the funny thing about it.", "docId": "110801pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "What should they be doing with their money right now?", "qSentId": 452}]